<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Use with Hugo on OpenGitDocs for Hugo</title>
    <link>https://opengitdocs.com/hugo/use-with-hugo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Use with Hugo on OpenGitDocs for Hugo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://opengitdocs.com/hugo/use-with-hugo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://opengitdocs.com/hugo/use-with-hugo/start/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://opengitdocs.com/hugo/use-with-hugo/start/</guid>
      <description>Build your OpenGitDocs site with Hugo static site generator.
1. Prepare Your Documentation Ensure your documentation is in the right format for use with Hugo static site generator. See Getting Started if you&amp;rsquo;re new to Hugo.
Here&amp;rsquo;s an example of what your content directory organization might look like:
content/ ├── _index.md ├── intro/ │ ├── config.md │ ├── deploy.md │ ├── _index.md │ ├── quickstart.md │ └── screenshot.png ├── support.md └── usage/ ├── customizing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configure Hugo</title>
      <link>https://opengitdocs.com/hugo/use-with-hugo/configure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://opengitdocs.com/hugo/use-with-hugo/configure/</guid>
      <description>Hugo expects a configuration file to build your site. OpenGitDocs includes one already set up; simply move it from the theme repository into your site root:
mv themes/opengitdocs/exampleSite/config.yaml . Be careful not to overwrite an existing file named config.yaml, if that is not your intention.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the full config.yaml used to build this site (yes, the one you&amp;rsquo;re reading right now!):
baseURL: https://opengitdocs.com/hugo/ languageCode: en-us title: OpenGitDocs for Hugo theme: # Name of your theme, hopefully, opengitdocs enableGitInfo: true # Show last modified date on pages sectionPagesMenu: main params: description: An open source static site solution for documentation websites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test and Build</title>
      <link>https://opengitdocs.com/hugo/use-with-hugo/test-and-build/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://opengitdocs.com/hugo/use-with-hugo/test-and-build/</guid>
      <description>Serve your new documentation site locally to see how it looks. Run:
hugo serve And visit http://localhost:1313/ in your browser to preview the site.
If everything seems lovely, you can build your site. Hugo will build to the public/ directory by default. To customize this, pass the -d flag and specify the destination directory.
For example, to build your site into your docs/ directory:
hugo -d docs/ Commit and push the changes back to your site repository.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>